redboxthanks.com 2010-12-26

# redbox

|  | 

Updated 08/11/10  

Thank you for visiting us online at redbox.com. At redbox, we strive to do everything we can to build the trust of our customers, and our commitment to your privacy is no exception. We are committed to protecting and safeguarding your privacy on the Internet, and, in this regard, are pleased to provide you with our Internet Privacy Policy. 

Redbox only gathers personal information, such as first and last names, addresses e-mail addresses and telephone numbers, when voluntarily submitted by you. For example, personal information may be collected from you in order to provide you with an e-mail receipt following a DVD rental or purchase transaction and to provide you with promotional offers or information. 

Occasionally, with your permission, we will send marketing information to you, such as discount offers, information about new product offerings, etc. If you do not elect to receive such materials, we will not send them to you. If you initially elect to receive such materials, but later change your mind, you may opt out from receiving such materials in the future by sending an e-mail to: [questions@redbox.com](mailto:questions@redbox.com)

Companies may from time to time be engaged by redbox to perform a variety of functions, such as fulfilling orders, assisting with promotions, providing technical services for our web site, etc. These companies may have access to personal information if needed to perform such functions. However, these companies may only use such personal information for the purpose of performing that function and may not use it for any other purpose. 

Redbox does not sell, transfer or disclose personal information to third parties. However, we may on occasion send marketing information on behalf of one of our business partners about products or services they provide that may be of interest to you. Redbox will not share your personal information with such partners but rather will send a mailing or email on behalf of those partners. 

Redbox reserves the right to use or disclose any information as needed to satisfy any law, regulation or legal request, to protect the integrity of the site, to fulfill your requests, or to cooperate in any law enforcement investigation or an investigation on a matter of public safety. 

You are in control of any personal information you provide to us on-line. If at any time you would like to correct the personal information we have about you or if you would like to change your preferences for contacts from us or on behalf of our business partners, you can let us know by contacting us at the email or postal address listed below. 

In order to review any personal information we have about you or to ask us to delete that information or to stop further use of the information, please e-mail us at [questions@redbox.com](mailto:questions@redbox.com). 

To help you personalize your online experience, redbox uses "Cookies." "Cookies" are alphanumeric identifiers that Redbox transfers to your hard drive through your Web browser to enable our system to recognize you and to provide features such as "remember me." Redbox also uses cookies to anonymously define new visitors, help analyze click-stream data, and track historical activity on the web site such as response to particular campaigns. 

Various vendors, including Google, show Redbox advertisements on sites on the internet. These vendors use cookies to display advertisements based on your visits to our website. You can opt-out of these vendors’ use of cookies by visiting the [Network Advertising Initiative opt-out page](http://networkadvertising.org/consumer/opt_out.asp). 

We may offer links to sites that are not operated by redbox. If you visit one of these linked sites, you should review their privacy and other policies. We are not responsible for the policies and practices of other companies, and any information you submit to those companies is subject to their privacy policies. 

This privacy policy is effective as of November 23, 2005. From time to time, it may be necessary for redbox to change this privacy policy. If we change our policy, we will post the revised version here, so we suggest that you check here periodically for the most up-to-date version of our privacy policy. Rest assured, however, that any changes will not be retroactively applied and will not alter how we handle previously collected information. 

To contact us by telephone, please call our Customer Support at 1.866.redbox3 (1.866.733.2693). 

To contact us by e-mail, please send your queries or comments to [questions@redbox.com](mailto:questions@redbox.com). 

To contact us by regular mail, please send to Redbox Automated Retail, LLC, One Tower Lane, Suite 1200, Oakbrook Terrace, IL 60181 

|   
---|---|---
